<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Services &#8211; Yi-Tsu Cheng, D.D.S. &amp; Associates</title>
	<atom:link href="https://dev.chengdds.com/service/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://dev.chengdds.com</link>
	<description>Dentist Chamblee GA &#124; (770) 457-3671</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 03:10:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.5</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Pediatric Dentistry Chamblee GA &#124; Kids Dentist</title>
		<link>https://dev.chengdds.com/service/pediatric-dentist</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 14:57:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dev.chengdds.com/?post_type=stm_service&#038;p=1787</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A replacement tooth, custom made to match your natural teeth. An implant is an artificial tooth root that is placed into your jaw to hold a replacement tooth or bridge. Dental prosthetics may be an option for people who have lost a tooth or teeth due to periodontal disease, an injury, or some other reason.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Planning for your child&rsquo;s first trip to the dentist can seem scary for both the parent and the child, but it doesn&rsquo;t have to be. If they need to see a dentist for a cleaning, or to have a cavity filled or x-rays were taken, it doesn&rsquo;t have to be overly difficult. Let&rsquo;s look at several tips for preparing for a trip to the dentist so that it&rsquo;s as simple as possible. As you plan for your child&rsquo;s trip...</p>
<p><a href="https://dev.chengdds.com/service/pediatric-dentist" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dental Implants Chamblee GA &#124; Replace Your Missing Teeth</title>
		<link>https://dev.chengdds.com/service/dental-implants-chamblee-ga</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 05:23:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dev.chengdds.com/?post_type=stm_service&#038;p=1573</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A replacement tooth, custom made to match your natural teeth. An implant is an artificial tooth root that is placed into your jaw to hold a replacement tooth or bridge. Dental prosthetics may be an option for people who have lost a tooth or teeth due to periodontal disease, an injury, or some other reason.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Each and every one of your teeth plays a vital role in the structure of your mouth as well as in relationship to your remaining teeth. A missing tooth can have serious consequences; aside from the aesthetics of having a gap in your smile, a missing tooth can affect the way you speak, alter your bite alignment and pressure (which can lead to uneven tooth wear), and lead to bone loss in your jaw.</p>
<p><a href="https://dev.chengdds.com/service/dental-implants-chamblee-ga" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Professional Teeth Whitening Chamblee GA</title>
		<link>https://dev.chengdds.com/service/teeth-whitening-service</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 04:49:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dev.chengdds.com/?post_type=stm_service&#038;p=1570</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Do you want a brighter smile? If you are unhappy with the color of your teeth, teeth whitening may be an excellent choice. Get the healthy, gorgeous smile you deserve today.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Over the past decade whiter teeth have become the norm, with consumers often identifying a brighter smile with youthfulness and good health. If you are unhappy with the color of your teeth, teeth whitening may be an excellent choice. But with so many options to choose from, how do you know which is right for you? It depends on a few things: the level of whitening you&rsquo;d like to achieve and the...</p>
<p><a href="https://dev.chengdds.com/service/teeth-whitening-service" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TMJ Treatment Chamblee GA</title>
		<link>https://dev.chengdds.com/service/tmj-options</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 19:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dev.chengdds.com/?post_type=stm_service&#038;p=1484</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Need TMJ treatment? TMJ (temporomandibular joint) disorders are a family of problems related to your complex jaw joint. Stop suffering from jaw pain today. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Temporomandibular joint and muscle disorders is commonly referred to as TMJ. This is actually a painful group of conditions that essentially affects the muscles that control the movement of the jaw. While pre-existing injuries play a role in a lot of cases of TMJ, sometimes symptoms start without any particular reason. The good news is, for a lot of people this kind of pain does not necessarily...</p>
<p><a href="https://dev.chengdds.com/service/tmj-options" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Invisalign Dentist Chamblee, GA &#124; Invisalign® Clear Braces</title>
		<link>https://dev.chengdds.com/service/invislign</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 06:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://dentall.stylemixthemes.com/demo/?post_type=stm_service&#038;p=1001</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Does Invisalign work better than traditional braces? You may think about popped brackets, loose wires, and missing out on your favorite foods for years. Call us today to choose the right Invisalign system for the comfortable and convenient way to straighten your teeth.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nobody looks forward to straightening their teeth. You may think about popped brackets, loose wires, and missing out on your favorite foods for years. Luckily, this perception is not always accurate. Tooth straightening has progressed beyond the days of metal braces or nothing. Invisalign clear aligners can get your teeth straight without the use of metal braces. If you do not need complicated...</p>
<p><a href="https://dev.chengdds.com/service/invislign" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dental Crowns Bridges Chamblee  GA&#124; Replace Your Missing Teeth</title>
		<link>https://dev.chengdds.com/service/crowns</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 09:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://dentall.stylemixthemes.com/demo/?post_type=stm_service&#038;p=894</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Do you need dental crowns and dental bridges? Crowns are often needed when a large cavity threatens the ongoing health of a tooth. Call us today to place high-quality permanent one-visit crowns or inlays without the usual two to three visits.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Dental Crown is a type of dental restoration which completely covers or encircles a tooth or implant. Crowns are often needed when a large cavity threatens the ongoing health of a tooth. They are typically bonded to the tooth using a dental cement. Crowns can be made from different materials like porcelain or Gold. Crowns are often used to improve the strength or appearance of teeth.</p>
<p><a href="https://dev.chengdds.com/service/crowns" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dental Implant Restoration Chamblee GA &#124; Dental Implant Repair</title>
		<link>https://dev.chengdds.com/service/dental-implants</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 09:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://dentall.stylemixthemes.com/demo/?post_type=stm_service&#038;p=893</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Do you have any difficulty with your dental implants? Call us today to help you restore your smile and confidence with their advanced technology that can produce new teeth in one day.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Each and every one of your teeth plays a vital role in the structure of your mouth as well as in relationship to your remaining teeth. A missing tooth can have serious consequences; aside from the aesthetics of having a gap in your smile, a missing tooth can affect the way you speak, alter your bite alignment and pressure (which can lead to uneven tooth wear), and lead to bone loss in your jaw.</p>
<p><a href="https://dev.chengdds.com/service/dental-implants" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Permanent Dental Bridge Dentist Chamblee GA</title>
		<link>https://dev.chengdds.com/service/dental-bridges</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 09:34:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://dentall.stylemixthemes.com/demo/?post_type=stm_service&#038;p=890</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tooth Loss? Dental bridges can be used to support crowns or dental implants to replace one or more. Call us today to restore your damaged teeth and replace missing teeth with dental crowns &#038; bridges. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A bridge, also called a &ldquo;fixed bridge&rdquo; or a &ldquo;fixed dental prosthesis,&rdquo; is a restoration that replaces one or more missing teeth. It extends across an area that has no, or missing teeth and is made up of an artificial tooth fused between 2 crowns. The bridge is held firmly in place by your own teeth on each side of the missing teeth, or by dental implants. A bridge is permanent and cannot be...</p>
<p><a href="https://dev.chengdds.com/service/dental-bridges" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cosmetic Dentist Chamblee GA</title>
		<link>https://dev.chengdds.com/service/cosmetic-dentistry</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 06:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://dentall.stylemixthemes.com/demo/?post_type=stm_service&#038;p=887</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Do you feel a shooting pain in your teeth when eating or drinking something hot?]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Top cosmetic dentistry is your ticket to a Beverly Hills smile. With veneers, teeth straightening, and teeth whitening, you may find that your friends and acquaintances cannot stop complimenting you on your dazzling smile. Hollywood movie stars may think of cosmetic dentistry as one more essential component as they dress for the red carpet, along with designer shoes and handbags...</p>
<p><a href="https://dev.chengdds.com/service/cosmetic-dentistry" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dental Veneers &#038; Laminates Chamblee GA &#124; Porcelain Veneers</title>
		<link>https://dev.chengdds.com/service/porcelain-veneers</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 06:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://dentall.stylemixthemes.com/demo/?post_type=stm_service&#038;p=886</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Do you need dental veneers? Veneers are made of thin, wafer-like porcelain shells that are customized to the exact shape, size, and color you desire. Call us today to adhere to the surface of your natural tooth, and instantly transform your appearance.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you hesitate when you smile, would like to increase your self-confidence, or prefer to eliminate any dental imperfections you may have, consider porcelain veneers. With veneers, the best smile of your dreams can become a reality after just a few appointments. Veneers are made of thin, wafer-like porcelain shells that are customized to the exact shape, size, and color you desire.</p>
<p><a href="https://dev.chengdds.com/service/porcelain-veneers" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Root Canal Treatment Chamblee GA &#124; Endodontic Specialists</title>
		<link>https://dev.chengdds.com/service/root-canal</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2015 04:53:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://dentall.stylemixthemes.com/demo/?post_type=stm_service&#038;p=478</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Do you need root canal treatment? A root canal is a procedure performed to save a tooth that is badly damaged or infected. Call us today to get the root canal treatment and help you feel better fast.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Root canal treatment, or Endodontic treatment, is the process of removing infected, injured or dead pulp from the tooth. The space inside the hard layers of each tooth is called the root canal system. This system is filled with soft dental pulp made up of nerves and blood vessels that help the tooth to develop. When bacteria (germs) enter your tooth through deep cavities...</p>
<p><a href="https://dev.chengdds.com/service/root-canal" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orthodontics Chamblee GA</title>
		<link>https://dev.chengdds.com/service/orthodontics</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2015 04:52:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://dentall.stylemixthemes.com/demo/?post_type=stm_service&#038;p=477</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Our hygienists clean teeth using professional equipment and pastes.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Orthodontics is the branch of dentistry that corrects teeth and jaws that are positioned improperly. Crooked teeth and teeth that do not fit together correctly are harder to keep clean, are at risk of being lost early due to tooth decay and periodontal disease, and cause extra stress on the chewing muscles that can lead to headaches, TMJ syndrome and neck, shoulder and back pain.</p>
<p><a href="https://dev.chengdds.com/service/orthodontics" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
