<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Articles &#8211; Yi-Tsu Cheng, D.D.S. &amp; Associates</title>
	<atom:link href="https://chengdds.com/category/articles/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://chengdds.com</link>
	<description>Dentist Chamblee GA &#124; (770) 457-3671</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 15:01:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>COVID-19 update</title>
		<link>https://chengdds.com/covid-19-update</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 14:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Articles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://chengdds.com/?p=2125</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[To our patients and community members, The unprecedented outbreak of COVID-19 has had a tremendous impact on our country and lives. As of late, our office hours have been very limited, with the main focus being on seeing major dental emergencies. Rest assured, we are carefully following all of the guidelines put forth by the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To our patients and community members, The unprecedented outbreak of COVID-19 has had a tremendous impact on our country and lives. As of late, our office hours have been very limited, with the main focus being on seeing major dental emergencies. Rest assured, we are carefully following all of the guidelines put forth by the CDC when seeing patients. It is our hope that this period of uncertainty...</p>
<p><a href="https://chengdds.com/covid-19-update" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why My Patients are Throwing Their Toothbrushes Away</title>
		<link>https://chengdds.com/why-my-patients-are-throwing-their-toothbrushes-away</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 14:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Articles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://chengdds.com/?p=1812</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Happy November! I am SO excited that the holidays are upon us! It’s one of my favorite times of the year! But unfortunately, if you are like many people this time of year is loaded with ALL the nasty germs that can ruin your holiday fun. What you probably may NOT realize, is that your...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Happy November! I am SO excited that the holidays are upon us! It’s one of my favorite times of the year! But unfortunately, if you are like many people this time of year is loaded with ALL the nasty germs that can ruin your holiday fun. What you probably may NOT realize, is that your oral hygiene often plays a factor in how often (and how long) you stay sick. So to help you get through this...</p>
<p><a href="https://chengdds.com/why-my-patients-are-throwing-their-toothbrushes-away" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>4 Kids Drinks That Have More Sugar Than Their Halloween Candy</title>
		<link>https://chengdds.com/4-kids-drinks-that-have-more-sugar-than-their-halloween-candy</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 21:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Articles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://chengdds.com/?p=1805</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Happy October! If you are anything like me, you are counting down the days to Halloween. It may come as a shock since I’m a dentist, but what can I say? I LOVE candy. (My favorites come in the form of chocolate bars!) Normally, I make it a point this time of year to stress...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Happy October! If you are anything like me, you are counting down the days to Halloween. It may come as a shock since I’m a dentist, but what can I say? I LOVE candy. (My favorites come in the form of chocolate bars!) Normally, I make it a point this time of year to stress the importance maintaining good dental hygiene to prevent damage to teeth (or dental gear) while enjoying extra treats.</p>
<p><a href="https://chengdds.com/4-kids-drinks-that-have-more-sugar-than-their-halloween-candy" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>3 Ways to Make Sure Your Breath is Date Night Fresh</title>
		<link>https://chengdds.com/3-ways-to-make-sure-your-breath-is-date-night-fresh</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 18:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Articles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://chengdds.com/?p=1792</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Happy September! Have you ever been in this situation? You are attending a wedding or important dinner and meet someone new, but you’re afraid to speak because you’re afraid your breath may stink. Even if you are diligent about flossing, brushing and using mouthwash, you wonder if it’s enough. &#160; Almost 25% of people suffer...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Happy September! Dentist Pediatric Chamblee GA Have you ever been in this situation? You are attending a wedding or important dinner and meet someone new, but you’re afraid to speak because you’re afraid your breath may stink. Even if you are diligent about flossing, brushing and using mouthwash, you wonder if it’s enough. Almost 25% of people suffer from the embarrassing condition of bad breath.</p>
<p><a href="https://chengdds.com/3-ways-to-make-sure-your-breath-is-date-night-fresh" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Protect Your Kid’s Smile (Without Ruining Their Fun)</title>
		<link>https://chengdds.com/how-to-protect-your-kids-smile-without-ruining-their-fun</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 02:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Articles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://chengdds.com/?p=1730</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Happy August! Do you remember that time the neighbor kid fell off his bike and hit his face on the sidewalk? It was BRUTAL. All the neighbors grimaced and held their breath until everything was checked out, and an “all clear” signal was given. It’s like a youth’s rite of passage. Kids between the ages...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Happy August! Do you remember that time the neighbor kid fell off his bike and hit his face on the sidewalk? It was BRUTAL. All the neighbors grimaced and held their breath until everything was checked out, and an “all clear” signal was given. It’s like a youth’s rite of passage. Kids between the ages of seven and 10, especially those who play baseball or basketball, have the highest number of...</p>
<p><a href="https://chengdds.com/how-to-protect-your-kids-smile-without-ruining-their-fun" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>5 Steps to Make Your Kid Comfortable in the Dentist&#8217;s Chair</title>
		<link>https://chengdds.com/dental-anxiety</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 23:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Articles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://chengdds.com/?p=1723</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As an adult, you already know that dental health is important. As a parent, you may be wondering at what point you need to start worrying about your child’s dental health. The short answer is, right now. Children can start developing cavities as soon as they have teeth. In fact, 42% of children have experienced...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As an adult, you already know that dental health is important. As a parent, you may be wondering at what point you need to start worrying about your child’s dental health. The short answer is, right now. Children can start developing cavities as soon as they have teeth. In fact, 42% of children have experienced tooth decay by age 11. And most of this is preventable by following good dental hygiene...</p>
<p><a href="https://chengdds.com/dental-anxiety" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Invisalign for Adults</title>
		<link>https://chengdds.com/invisalign-for-adults</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 03:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Articles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://chengdds.com/?p=1672</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We believe you’re never too old to straighten your teeth. Many of our patients are adults who are currently undergoing treatment. Did you know that roughly 30 percent of all orthodontic patients these days are adults? Whether you had braces as a teen but your teeth have shifted, or you have never undergone orthodontics but...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We believe you’re never too old to straighten your teeth. Many of our patients are adults who are currently undergoing treatment. Did you know that roughly 30 percent of all orthodontic patients these days are adults? Whether you had braces as a teen but your teeth have shifted, or you have never undergone orthodontics but always wanted to, we can help you enjoy straighter teeth, an improved bite...</p>
<p><a href="https://chengdds.com/invisalign-for-adults" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Your Travel Guide To Antique Row And More In Chamblee GA</title>
		<link>https://chengdds.com/travel-guide-antique-row-chamblee-ga</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 01:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Articles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://chengdds.com/?p=1592</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[You are really going to enjoy this travel guide for Chamblee GA. There are some really unique places of interest, and I explored some of them with you in a past article about three of the top things to do when you visit Chamblee. I am going to give those three attractions a mention, and...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You are really going to enjoy this travel guide for Chamblee GA. There are some really unique places of interest, and I explored some of them with you in a past article about three of the top things to do when you visit Chamblee. I am going to give those three attractions a mention, and then I am going to give you details about all the other great attractions that await you in Chamblee, Georgia.</p>
<p><a href="https://chengdds.com/travel-guide-antique-row-chamblee-ga" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Are The Best Vacation Rentals When Traveling To Chamblee GA?</title>
		<link>https://chengdds.com/best-vacation-rentals-traveling-chamblee-ga</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 01:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Articles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://chengdds.com/?p=1590</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Chamblee GA is one of the most interesting small city vacation destinations I have written about recently. It didn&#8217;t take much looking around before I ran into Antique Row. And Broad Street isn&#8217;t even the only place in the city where you can find antique shops. Plus you have the gigantic flea market, the Plaza...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chamblee GA is one of the most interesting small city vacation destinations I have written about recently. It didn’t take much looking around before I ran into Antique Row. And Broad Street isn’t even the only place in the city where you can find antique shops. Plus you have the gigantic flea market, the Plaza Fiesta and much more. You are certainly excited about your upcoming trip...</p>
<p><a href="https://chengdds.com/best-vacation-rentals-traveling-chamblee-ga" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Plan A Trip Around These Top Three Things To Do In Chamblee GA</title>
		<link>https://chengdds.com/plan-trip-around-top-three-things-chamblee-ga</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 01:06:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Articles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://chengdds.com/?p=1588</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Do you like antiques? If you do, you are absolutely going to love visiting Chamblee GA because many of its top attractions are all about antiquing. There are plenty of other adventures to be had, too. In this article, we are going to look at the top three things to do in Chamblee, Georgia. Hopefully,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you like antiques? If you do, you are absolutely going to love visiting Chamblee GA because many of its top attractions are all about antiquing. There are plenty of other adventures to be had, too. In this article, we are going to look at the top three things to do in Chamblee, Georgia. Hopefully, you find yourself excited about planning a trip to this small and charming city outside of Atlanta.</p>
<p><a href="https://chengdds.com/plan-trip-around-top-three-things-chamblee-ga" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Are The Best Hotels In Chamblee GA For Booking A Vacation?</title>
		<link>https://chengdds.com/best-hotels-chamblee-ga-booking-vacation</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 01:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Articles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://chengdds.com/?p=1586</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[During your stay in Chamblee GA, I bet you plan to shop Antique Row. It seems like that is the biggest reason to travel to this city right outside of Atlanta. When you arrive, you are going to need to have plans for lodging. Where are you going to stay? Let&#8217;s take a look at...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>During your stay in Chamblee GA, I bet you plan to shop Antique Row. It seems like that is the biggest reason to travel to this city right outside of Atlanta. When you arrive, you are going to need to have plans for lodging. Where are you going to stay? Let’s take a look at some of the best hotels you can choose from when it comes to taking a vacation in Chamblee, Georgia. One of the top hotels is...</p>
<p><a href="https://chengdds.com/best-hotels-chamblee-ga-booking-vacation" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Five Chamblee GA Restaurants That Rank Near The Top</title>
		<link>https://chengdds.com/five-chamblee-ga-restaurants-rank-near-top</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 00:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Articles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://chengdds.com/?p=1584</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[You know the city of Chamblee is close to Atlanta when the #1 ranked restaurant on a top travel site for the small city is actually located in the capital city. Let&#8217;s skip over the Atlanta restaurants, however, that have landed a spot on the Chamblee restaurant rankings. There are 52 listed restaurants currently in...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You know the city of Chamblee is close to Atlanta when the #1 ranked restaurant on a top travel site for the small city is actually located in the capital city. Let’s skip over the Atlanta restaurants, however, that have landed a spot on the Chamblee restaurant rankings. There are 52 listed restaurants currently in the city of Chamblee, Georgia. We are going to look at the top five.</p>
<p><a href="https://chengdds.com/five-chamblee-ga-restaurants-rank-near-top" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Valuable Suggestions When You Need a Dentist</title>
		<link>https://chengdds.com/valuable-suggestions-need-dentist</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 06:53:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Articles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://chengdds.com/?p=1581</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When you hire a dentist, they are responsible for a lot more than simply filling cavities and such. Given the fact that everything in your body is in some way or another connected; having troubles in your mouth can easily affect other parts too. This is why it is crucial that your dentist be trustworthy...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When you hire a dentist, they are responsible for a lot more than simply filling cavities and such. Given the fact that everything in your body is in some way or another connected; having troubles in your mouth can easily affect other parts too. This is why it is crucial that your dentist be trustworthy and for you to be assured of his competency. In this article, you will find some great advice...</p>
<p><a href="https://chengdds.com/valuable-suggestions-need-dentist" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Options to Consider When Looking for a Dentist</title>
		<link>https://chengdds.com/options-consider-looking-dentist</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 06:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Articles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://chengdds.com/?p=1578</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If you are fortunate enough to have a good reliable dentist; you will have comfort in knowing you will be giving appropriate treatment when needed. If you procrastinate and do not find a reliable dentist before they may be needed, you could regret it later on. Below, you will find some valuable information that will...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you are fortunate enough to have a good reliable dentist; you will have comfort in knowing you will be giving appropriate treatment when needed. If you procrastinate and do not find a reliable dentist before they may be needed, you could regret it later on. Below, you will find some valuable information that will aid your search for a reliable dentist that will keep your teeth and gums healthy.</p>
<p><a href="https://chengdds.com/options-consider-looking-dentist" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Important Points to Keep in Mind When Hiring a New Dentist</title>
		<link>https://chengdds.com/important-points-keep-mind-hiring-new-dentist</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 06:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Articles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://chengdds.com/?p=1575</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Keeping your teeth healthy will be easier when you have the right dentist. You can&#8217;t find any substitute for dental care that is high quality, but you can do plenty on your own, like flossing and brushing. Cavities happen no matter how careful you are, so dental procedures, such as root canals or fillings, are...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Keeping your teeth healthy will be easier when you have the right dentist. You can’t find any substitute for dental care that is high quality, but you can do plenty on your own, like flossing and brushing. Cavities happen no matter how careful you are, so dental procedures, such as root canals or fillings, are inevitable. In this article, we’ll be looking at ways to find the best dentist for your...</p>
<p><a href="https://chengdds.com/important-points-keep-mind-hiring-new-dentist" rel="nofollow">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
